- So you're okay with me cutting the final rope?
-所以我可以剪最后一根绳子吗？
- [Speaker In Blue] Oh my god.
-[蓝色的发言者]天哪。
- We're cutting the final rope!
-我们在剪最后的绳子！
(dramatic rock music)| Three, two, one, cut!
（戏剧性的摇滚音乐）|三，二，一切！
This could equal a million dollars.
这可能相当于一百万美元。
(shouting) (splashing)
（大喊）（溅起）
(video rewinding)
（视频倒带）
How's it feel?
感觉如何？
- It's kind of scary.
-有点吓人。
- [Host] And welcome to the number two slot.
-[主持人]欢迎来到第二号位。
How do you feel?
你觉得怎么样？
- I'm good, I'm ready to win.
-我很好，我准备赢了。
- [Host] Is this easy or harder
-[主持人]这容易还是难？
than you thought it would be?
比您想象的要大？
- I'm not gonna say 'cause y'all are gonna make it harder.
-我不会说，因为你们都会变得更难。
- [Host] How do you feel?
-[主持人]您感觉如何？
- Freaking out, not gonna lie.
-吓坏了，不会撒谎。
I have huge fear of heights.
我对高地高度恐惧。
- [Host] Last one of you guys to fall
-[主持人]你们最后一个摔倒了
into this pool of water,
进入这池水，
gets the chance at one million dollars.
获得一百万美元的机会。
- No way!
- 没门！
- And here's what I mean by that.
-这就是我的意思。
We are going four last to leave videos
我们要最后四个离开视频
and the winners of each will compete in a fifth video
每个获奖者将参加第五个视频比赛
for one million dollars.
一百万美元。
You are currently watching part one of this series.
您目前正在观看本系列的第一部分。
I don't care who wins,
我不在乎谁赢了
but whoever does, will fly back in a few weeks
但是不管谁，都会在几周后飞回来
and compete against the other winners for a million dollars.
并与其他获胜者竞争一百万美元。
This is arguably the most extreme thing we've ever done.
可以说这是我们做过的最极端的事情。
See this cage?
看到这个笼子了吗？
We took it from American Warrior Ninja, that thing.
我们从美国战士忍者那里拿走的。
We put some ropes and we put some people on it.
我们放了一些绳子，我们放了一些人。
And we grabbed a million dollars
我们抢到了一百万美元
and that's how we ended up here.
这就是我们到这里为止的方式。
So as I said Chris, we're doing four last to leaves,
正如我所说的克里斯，我们正在做最后四次离开，
this is the first one.
这是第一个。
And the winners of all four compete in a fifth one
而所有四个的获胜者将参加第五个比赛
for one million dollars.
一百万美元。
Which means there's three more.
这意味着还有三个。
- So how you gonna pick all the other people?
-那么你该如何挑选所有其他人？
- I'm glad you asked.
-很高兴你问。
Here's how.
这是如何做。
If you buy merch, or follow me on Instagram,
如果您购买商品或在Instagram上关注我，
you'll be entered.
您将被输入。
It's that simple.
就这么简单。
We're gonna randomly pick people who follow me on Instagram
我们将随机选择在Instagram上关注我的人
or people who buy merch in between now
或现在之间购买商品的人
and the next few challenges
以及接下来的几个挑战
and we're gonna invite 'em down to compete.
我们将邀请他们参加比赛。
And I'll remind you about that at the end of the video.
我会在视频结尾提醒您。
So we gave each of you guys a coach
所以我们给你们每个人一个教练
and we made them wear the same shirt
我们让他们穿同一件衬衫
so the viewers could tell.
这样观众才能知道。
Cameron, your coach is Chris.
卡梅隆，你的教练是克里斯。
Alberto you have Marcus.
阿尔贝托，你有马库斯。
Colby, we brought you a Chandler,
科尔比，我们为您带来了钱德勒，
so you can just go ahead and just get out now
所以你可以继续前进，现在就出去
if you want to. - No!
如果你想。 -不！
Don't say that!
不要这样说！
- [Host] And you are assigned the big guy.
-[主持人]您被指派为大人物。
So there you go, you each have a coach,
所以你们去了，你们每个人都有一位教练，
they'll get you whatever you need.
他们将为您提供所需的一切。
Whoever falls last gets to move on
最后跌倒的人继续前进
and compete for one million dollars, good luck.
争夺一百万美元，祝你好运。
- I want to see if I can get you a bottle of water
-我想看看能不能给你一瓶水
like up there, let's give it a shot.
喜欢在那里，让我们试一试。
Kobe! - Ah, oh!
科比！ -啊！
- Cameron, this matches your shirt.
-卡梅伦，这和你的衬衫相配。
(grunting) (laughing)
（咕run）（笑）
- [Host] Oh good catch!
-[主持人]不错！
- A banana for you. (banana whizzing)
-给你的香蕉。 （香蕉嘶嘶声）
A banana for you! - Wait, wait, wait.
给你的香蕉！ -等一下，等一下。
- Hello! - Whoa!
- 你好！ -哇！
(exclaiming) (clapping)
（惊呼）（拍手）
- [Chris] He didn't even move!
-[克里斯]他甚至都没有动！
(upbeat electronic music)
（欢乐的电子音乐）
- Uh, huh, uh, huh, huh, uh, huh.
-恩，恩，恩，恩，恩
- So Chris, we're gonna do our first challenge.
-克里斯，我们要做第一个挑战。
There's seats behind you
你身后有座位
and you can earn time for sitting to help you win.
而且您可以腾出时间坐下来帮助您获胜。
The first challenge for one minute of sitting,
坐一分钟的第一个挑战，
you have to throw your contestant this egg,
你必须把这个鸡蛋丢给你的选手
and he has to toss it back, without a crack.
他必须将其扔回去，而不会裂开。
And if you do that, he can sit.
如果您这样做，他可以坐下。
- Dude, I was never good at sports, underhand.
-杜德，我从来都不擅长运动。
(exclaiming) (egg splashing)
（惊呼）（蛋溅）
- All right. (laughing)
- 好吧。 （笑）
- Bloop!
-Bloop！
- All right, Marcus.
-好吧，马库斯。
- Oh my God.
- 哦，我的上帝。
- Here's an egg.
-这是一个鸡蛋。
- Great shot! - And if Chandler catches this
- 好球！ -如果钱德勒抓住了这个
you get to sit.
你坐下。
Ooh there we go! (clapping)
哦，我们去！ （拍手）
And no cracks.
而且没有裂缝。
So since they completed the egg challenge,
因此，既然他们完成了鸡蛋挑战赛，
she gets a little bit of sitting time.
她有一点坐时间。
There's your seat.
坐吧
Colby gets to sit for the next minute.
科尔比坐下一分钟。
Congrats! (slapping)
恭喜！ （拍打）
You're helping your contestant.
您正在帮助您的参赛者。
While Colby's wrapping up her sitting time,
当科尔比（Colby）结束她的坐姿时，
let's see if you can earn him some.
让我们看看你是否可以赚到他一些。
- Perfect! (gasping)
-太好了！ （喘气）
- Ah! (clapping)
-啊！ （拍手）
- It is perfect.
- 这十分完美。
I will lower the seat.
我将降低座位。
So, Colby, your minute is up, stand up.
因此，Colby，您的会议纪要站起来了。
Try not to fall.
尽量不要跌倒。
And now we will take her seat back.
现在我们将她带回座位。
And Jake's contestant wants some sitting time,
杰克的参赛者想要一些休息时间，
so we give him his seat. - Coming down behind ya!
所以我们给他座位。 -来呀！
(clapping) - There it is, yeah!
（拍手）-是的，是的！
- One final thing,
-最后一件事，
if your contestant wins,
如果您的参赛者获胜，
they go on to compete for a million dollars.
他们继续争夺一百万美元。
To incentivize you guys to help your players win,
为了激励大家帮助您的球员获胜，
if they win the million dollars, they have to give you 10%.
如果他们赢得一百万美元，他们必须给您10％。
- Ooh, you better win. - To incentivize you guys.
-哦，你最好赢。 -激励你们。
- I'll get you anything you need.
-我会为您提供所需的任何东西。
- That's $100 grand, and they still win $900 grand.
-那是$ 100大奖，而他们仍然赢得$ 900大奖。
Now that you guys also have money on the line,
现在你们也有钱了，
let's do the egg challenge again, but from further back.
让我们再做一次鸡蛋挑战，但要从更远的地方开始。
This time it's for five minutes instead of one.
这次是五分钟而不是一分钟。
Don't cross that, we have a million dollars on the line
不要越过，我们有一百万美元
and our markers a bag of chips.
我们的标记器是一袋筹码。
This time we'll just do if he catches it.
这次如果他抓到我们就去做。
He can sit for five minutes.
他可以坐五分钟。
(soft synthesized music) (gasping)
（软合成音乐）（喘气）
- Aw! - It's good!
-噢！ - 很好！
- [Chandler] Did that go between his legs?
-[钱德勒]那是在他的双腿之间吗？
- Yeah it did.
-是的
- Not it. - Nope.
- 不是。 - 不。
(smacking) - Oh!
（打喷嚏）-哦！
(growling)
（咆哮）
- That's five minutes.
-五分钟
I'll go lower it.
我会降低它。
- Here you go Colby.
-在这里，你去科尔比。
- I bet he's not gonna catch it.
-我敢打赌他不会抓住它的。
(egg splattering) - Oh no!
（蛋溅）-哦，不！
- Does that count?
-算在内吗？
(egg splattering) (exclaiming)
（蛋溅）（惊呼）
- Oh my gosh!
- 天啊！
Sports, not good at 'em.
运动，不擅长运动。
So who thinks they're in first place right now?
那么谁认为他们现在处于第一位呢？
- I mean, honestly, right here.
-老实说，我的意思是在这里。
- You think you're first place?
-你以为是第一名？
- Yeah. - Who's that?
-是的- 那是谁？
(heavy rock music) (siren wailing)
（重摇滚音乐）（警笛声）
- That was sabotage.
-那是破坏活动。
You have to do ten laps around the pool.
您必须在游泳池周围做十圈。
You can't throw things at the competitors!
您不能向竞争对手扔东西！
- I can do what I want!
-我可以做我想做的！
- When I smell sabotage, the lights turn red
-当我闻到破坏活动时，指示灯变红
and the alarm comes out. (siren wailing)
然后警报响起。 （警笛声）
- Oh this is gonna be cold. (upbeat polka music)
-哦，这会很冷的。 （欢乐的波尔卡音乐）
(water splashing) (exclaiming)
（泼水）（惊呼）
Ack, it's so cold!
阿克，好冷！
(upbeat polka music)
（欢乐的波尔卡音乐）
Well there we go, that's one lap.
好了，我们走了，那是一圈。
- This is what happens to sabotagers here.
-这就是在这里破坏者的身份。
- I'm cold!
- 我觉得冷！
(suspenseful instrumental music)
（悬念器乐）
- Its getting a bit more difficult.
-变得越来越困难。
- Now it's time for our first incentive.
-现在是我们第一个奖励的时候了。
This is the unicorn of gifts.
这是礼物的独角兽。
First person to get out,
第一个离开的人，
can have an iPhone, Airpods, Beats, and PS4.
可以拥有iPhone，Airpods，Beats和PS4。
Just consider it, I don't care who it is.
只是考虑一下，我不在乎它是谁。
(crickets chirping)
（cri）
- Nobody, really?
-真的吗？
- No one wants the unicorn of love?
-没有人想要爱的独角兽吗？
- All right, they're being stubborn,
-好吧，他们很固执，
someone give me a knife. - Wait a minute, what?
有人给我一把刀。 -等一下
- Things are lasting a while,
-事情持续了一段时间，
red light me. (ominous electronic music)
红色点亮我。 （不祥的电子音乐）
Ooh there we go! (laughing and hollering)
哦，我们去！ （大笑）
- [Host] We'll just cut this rope.
-[主持人]我们要剪短绳。
- Hey, don't cut the rope! - Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
-嘿，别割了绳子！ -哇，哇，哇，哇！
No, no-- - Ooh.
不，不--哦。
- They're down to 16 ropes.
-他们只有16条绳索。
- Oh you're going again, oh. - Fifteen.
-哦，你又要去了，哦。 -十五岁
Five of those twenty ropes are gone, how does it feel?
那二十根绳索中有五根消失了，感觉如何？
- There's a big difference but--
-有很大的不同，但是-
- I don't believe you, I'm cutting more.
-我不相信你，我正在削减更多。
All right, turn the lights back to normal, we're good.
好吧，把灯恢复正常，我们很好。
- Try again. (bottle crunching)
- 再试一次。 （嘎吱嘎吱）
- You almost got him out! (laughing)
-你差点把他赶出去！ （笑）
- My bad!
- 我的错！ （笑）
(festive bell music)
（节日钟声）
(ropes snapping) (exclaiming and laughing)
（啪啪声）（大笑）
- You guys have ten minutes
-你们有十分钟
to draw a portrait of your contestant.
画出你的选手的肖像。
I will then let people on my social media vote with a poll
然后，我将让我的社交媒体上的人进行投票
for the best one.
为最好的。
The viewers will decide.
观众将决定。
Whoever they vote, gets ten minutes of sitting down.
无论他们投票谁，都可以坐下十分钟。
Three, two, one. (clapping)
三二一。 （拍手）
(energetic banjo music)
（充满活力的班卓琴音乐）
You know Chandler, I can't say I'm impressed.
你知道钱德勒，我不能说给我留下深刻的印象。
- You can't tell what that is though?
-你不知道那是什么吗？
It looks exactly like what she's doing, right?
看起来就像她在做什么，对不对？
- [Host] Oh Chris that looks good.
-[主持人]克里斯，看起来不错。
Trees are lit.
树木被点燃。
(energetic banjo music)
（充满活力的班卓琴音乐）
- All right, you ready for this?
-好吧，你准备好了吗？
- Oh, that's actually not that bad.
-哦，那还算不错。
- Get ready for this masterpiece son.
-为这个杰作儿子做好准备。
(gasping) Do you like it?
（喘着粗气）你喜欢吗？
- I love it. - You see it, right?
- 我喜欢它。 -看到了吧？
- Uh, yeah, no?
-恩，是吗？
- No?
-不？
- Are you ready for this?
- 你准备好了吗？
- That is awesome I like the looser signs on it.
-太棒了，我喜欢上面的宽松标志。
- I drew everything.
-我画了一切。
So I think this is a winner, you know?
所以我认为这是赢家，知道吗？
- Are you ready for the beautiful?
-准备好迎接美丽了吗？
I got the peach fuzz and everything,
我得到了桃子的绒毛和所有的东西，
it's got a W on your chest, you wanna know why?
它的胸口有W，您想知道为什么吗？
Winter.
冬季。
- So I put a poll out on social media,
-所以我在社交媒体上进行了民意调查，
which by the way, follow my Instagram
顺便说一句，跟随我的Instagram
if you wanna potentially be here, next competition.
如果您想在这里参加下一场比赛。
But regardless, I let you guys vote.
但是不管怎样，我让你们投票。
And you guys decided that Jake is the winner.
你们决定杰克是赢家。
- What?
- 什么？ - 什么？
- Yup. (dramatic orchestral music)
- 对。 （戏剧性的管弦乐）
The winner of nothing, Chris actually won!
没事的赢家，克里斯实际上赢了！
- Yeah! (laughing)
-是的！ （笑）
- So sad. (board tapping)
- 好难过。 （攻丝）
- It didn't work. (painting dropping)
-没用。 （绘画掉落）
- Oh how does that feel man?
-哦，那个人感觉如何？
- It feels amazing!
-感觉很棒！
- [Chris] Look at him, he's laying all the way back!
-[克里斯]看着他，他一直在躺着！
You guys are jelly right now.
你们现在是果冻。
(marching band music)
（乐队音乐）
- [Host] It's been getting pretty tough,
-[主持人]事情变得越来越艰难了，
so I want you to call a family member
所以我想你打电话给家人
and try to get some motivation.
并尝试获得一些动力。
Hey, how's it going? (chuckling)
嘿，最近怎么样？ （咯咯笑）
Your brother is suspended above a pool,
你哥哥被悬在水池上方，
and there's four other people,
还有另外四个人，
whoever gets out last gets to compete for a million dollars.
谁最后走出去就可以争夺一百万美元。
- Oh my gosh.
- 天啊。
- Hey mom, so I didn't tell you,
-嘿，妈妈，我没告诉你，
'cause you'd go off on me probably.
因为你可能会拒绝我。
- [Colby's Mom] Why aren't you calling from your cell phone?
-[Colby的妈妈]你为什么不用手机打电话？
- Mom, it's a competition, I can't have my phone.
-妈妈，这是比赛，我没有电话。
I'm competing to win a million dollars.
我正在争夺一百万美元。
- She's saying oh my God are you serious.
-她是说哦，天哪，你是认真的。
- Hey what's up dad?
-嘿，爸爸怎么了？
If I win this one, then I go back in December
如果我赢了，那我在十二月
and have a chance to win a million dollars.
并有机会赢得一百万美元。
- [Cameron's Dad] You what?
-[Cameron的爸爸]你呢？
That's great man.
太好了
- All right contestants,
-好的参赛者，
the unicorn of wealth is coming back.
财富的独角兽又回来了。
For whoever gets out next, we have some Beats, some Airpods,
对于接下来要离开的人，我们有一些节拍，一些Airpods，
an iPhone, an Xbox 1, a PS4,
iPhone，Xbox 1，PS4，
that's what was up there earlier.
那就是早些时候在那里。
And now, we're adding in a MacBook Pro.
现在，我们添加了MacBook Pro。
(exclaiming)
（惊呼）
And some PS4 video games.
和一些PS4视频游戏。
All you have to do is get out now and you can have 'em.
您所要做的就是立即离开，然后可以拥有它们。
Even if you win here today,
就算今天赢了
you're not guaranteed a million dollars.
您不能保证获得一百万美元。
- That's a lot of stuff though.
-不过很多。
- It's about $3,500 dollars.
-大约3500美元。
- Go ahead and do it, somebody do it.
-继续做，有人做。
- See right about now is when Chandler would get out.
-马上看看钱德勒什么时候出来。
- Actually way earlier. - Yeah, way earlier.
-实际上早。 -是的，早一点。
- No I'm just sayin' like that's a lot of stuff man,
-不，我只是说，这是很多人的事，
like you know, if you go along way with that--
就像您知道的那样，如果您继续这样做-
- So is a million dollars. - I know.
-一百万美元也是如此。 - 我知道。
- He's considering it.
-他正在考虑。
- Do it, do it! - You gotta jump now!
-做吧，做吧！ -你现在要跳！
(melancholy instrumental music)
（忧郁的器乐）
- [Emperor Palpatine] You're fulfilling your destiny.
-[Emperor Palpatine]您正在实现自己的命运。
(water splashing) (slow motion shouting)
（泼水）（慢动作大喊）
- (slow motion exclaiming) Yeah!
-（慢动作呼喊）是的！
- (slow motion shouting) No, that's so cold!
-（慢动作大喊）不，太冷了！
(water splashing) (exclaiming)
（泼水）（惊呼）
- Oh! - No, that's so cold!
-哦！ -不，太冷了！
- What would your mother say to you right now?
-你妈妈现在会对你说什么？
- Oh my God he gave up a million dollars!
-天哪，他放弃了一百万美元！
He gave up 900 bands and gave up your hundred.
他放弃了900支乐队，放弃了您的一百支乐队。
- We have three more of these, where you'll also be a coach
-我们还有另外三个，您也将在其中担任教练
and so you still have other chances.
因此您还有其他机会。
Follow me on Instagram or buy merch,
在Instagram上关注我或购买商品，
you could have a chance.
你可能会有机会
- So here's all your items.
-这是您的所有物品。
- Tell me how you were feeling when you were up there.
-告诉我你在那儿的感觉如何。
- I was already in pain,
-我已经很痛苦了
it feels good not to be up there anymore though.
感觉很好，但是不再在那里。
- Yeah. - It's no joke.
-是的-这不是开玩笑。
- You were up there for 13 hours.
-你在那里呆了13个小时。
- 13 hours, man!
-13个小时，老兄！
- Well, thanks for coming, appreciate it.
-好，谢谢您的光临，谢谢。
I hope you had fun. - Yeah.
我希望你玩得开心。 -是的
- Alberto, you did a good job, bro.
-Alberto，您做得不错，兄弟。
- [Host] So there's only three of you now.
-[主持人]所以你们只有三个。
How does that make you feel?
那让你感觉如何？
- I feel hyped, yeah, I feel optimistic.
-我感到很炒作，是的，我感到乐观。
- [Host] Colby, how do you feel now that he's gone?
-[主持人]科尔比，现在他走了，您感觉如何？
- I'm ready, I'm hyped.
-我准备好了，我被炒作了。
- [Host] How about you Cameron?
-[主持人]你的卡梅伦怎么样？
- I feel like I got more space
-我觉得我有更多的空间
to kind of just do what I want
只是做我想要的
and I feel more confident now.
我现在变得更加自信。
- [Host] One of you will get the chance
-[主持人]你们其中一位将有机会
at winning a million dollars, the other two, nothing,
赢得一百万美元，另外两个，什么都没有，
so, good luck.
所以，祝你好运。
She's moving over to close the gap.
她正在移动以缩小差距。
- [Marcus] In honor of Alberto's exit, we should cut a rope.
-[马库斯]为了纪念阿尔贝托的离开，我们应该剪一条绳子。
- You're right actually.
-你说得对。
- In honor of his exit.
-为了纪念他的退出。
Red lights.
红灯。
We stated with twenty ropes, we're down to 15.
我们用二十根绳子说到15条。
I think we'll just do this.
我认为我们会这样做。
So now we're down to 14.
所以现在我们降至14。
Now we're just gonna, 13.
现在我们就要13岁了。
I'll let you guys vote,
我让你们投票
should I cut one more? - No.
我应该再剪一个吗？ -不
- [Host] What do you think Akira?
-[主持人]您如何看待Akira？
- Yeah. - Colby what do you think?
-是的-科尔比，您如何看待？
- I mean, obviously. - Okay, that's two yeses.
-很明显。 -好的，是两个。
Whoa, they wanna get this over with.
哇，他们想解决这个问题。
If I cut another, that puts us at 12.
如果我再砍下一个，那我们就十二岁了。
- Wow. - We're droppin' ropes.
- 哇。 -我们在扎绳子。
Twelve it is. - Wow.
是十二点。 - 哇。
- You guys are running out of things to stand on.
-你们没什么东西可以站了。
Lights back to normal, we'll cut some more ropes later.
灯光恢复正常，我们稍后再剪一些绳子。
Just kidding, turn the red lights back on.
只是开玩笑，重新打开红灯。
(chuckling) - Oh my God.
（咯咯笑）-天哪。
Dude he's not playing with them!
老兄，他不跟他们玩！
- Sike!  that was just a joke, normal lights.
-ike！那只是个玩笑，正常的灯光。
(gentle electronic music)
（轻柔的电子音乐）
- How many hours have been up here?
-这里有几个小时了？
- [Tareq] Chrissy, wakie, wakie.
-[Tareq] Chrissy，wakie，wakie。
Jakie, wakie, wakie.
杰基，基基，基基。
Why is there a french fry on his head?
为什么他的头上有炸薯条？
Each of you three still have a contestant left.
你们三个仍然每个都剩下一名选手。
What do you want to say to Cameron?
您想对金马伦说什么？
- He knows he's a beast and a warrior.
-他知道他是野兽和战士。
- [Host] What do you want to say?
-[主持人]您想说什么？
- You're doing amazing.
-你做的很棒。
- You? (snoring)
-你呢？ （打呼））
Awesome, if someone gets out within the next minute,
太好了，如果某人在下一分钟内下车，
I'll give them $5,000 dollars.
我给他们5,000美元。
(water splashing) (upbeat instrumental music)
（泼水）（欢乐的器乐）
- (in slow motion) He knows he's a beast and a warrior.
-（慢动作）他知道他是野兽和战士。
You love to see it. (exclaiming)
您喜欢看它。 （惊呼）
- That's what you wake up to today.
-那就是你今天醒来的。
- I tried man, I was dying for a long time up there.
-我尝试过男人，我在那里已经死了很长时间。
- You could've had it easy man.
-你本来可以轻松的。
- He looks like he's going pretty strong.
-他看起来很强壮。
- [Host] What are you going to do with that $5,000?
-[主持人]那5,000美元您打算怎么办？
- I'm gonna donate some trees, maybe go do some shopping.
-我要捐些树，也许去逛街。
- He tried his best,
-他尽力了
hey, at least he didn't go home empty handed.
嘿，至少他没有空手回家。
Poor Colby's gonna go home empty handed.
可怜的科尔比要空手回家。
- [Host] Your contestant and your contestant remain.
-[主持人]您的参赛者和您的参赛者保留。
- Yeah.
-是的
- [Host] Now that Cameron is gone, it is you two fighting
-[主持人]卡梅伦（Cameron）走了，那是你们两个人的战斗
for a chance at one million dollars.
有机会获得一百万美元。
- Whoo!
-哇！
- [Host] So we'll start off with you Colby.
-[主持人]因此，我们将与您开始Colby。
Cameron's gone, how you feeling?
卡梅伦走了，​​你感觉如何？
- I'm feeling even more confident.
-我感到更加自信。
I'm here to win that million.
我在这里赢得那百万。
- [Host] How 'bout you, how are things going now?
-[主持人]拜托您，现在情况如何？
- 48.
-48。
- He's lasted 48 hours? - 48, let's go!
-他持续了48个小时？ -48，走吧！
- [Host] Okay, whenever you get tired remember,
-[主持人]好的，每当您累了时，请记住，
a million dollars is a lot
一百万美元是很多
and your brother would be really sad if you didn't win it.
如果你不赢，你的兄弟会很难过。
Okay have fun.
好吧，玩得开心。
(upbeat electronic music)
（欢乐的电子音乐）
So Chandler had to leave,
所以钱德勒不得不离开，
so we're gonna put you in charge of Colby.
因此，我们将由您负责Colby。
- Boo. (laughing)
-嘘（笑）
- For the next minute,
-接下来的一分钟
it'll be ten grand if someone gets out,
如果有人下车，那将是十点钟
then it drops back to seven.
然后回落到7。
- You can do better Akira.
-可以做得更好。
- You have 55 seconds to decide,
-您有55秒的时间来决定，
and then it falls back to seven grand.
然后回落到七大。
- That's pushing it, that's a lot.
-推动了很多。
- You have 40 seconds to win ten grand.
-您有40秒的时间赢得十个大奖。
You could just lose in the million dollar round
你可能在百万美元的回合中输了
and get nothing, when right now,
一无所获
you could walk away with ten grand.
你可以带着十个宏伟的身子走开。
- Ten grand, we were waiting on this.
-十点盛大，我们正在等待。
- Akira, you could take that 10K and split it with your twin
-晃，你可以拿这10K分成两张
he's be happy with you.
他对你很高兴。
- Or you can play for this million
-或者你可以为这百万
and potentially win a million dollars.
并有可能赢得一百万美元。
- But we're in it to win it.
-但是我们要赢得它。
- Yeah!
-是的！
- Five, four, three, two-- - We came to win,
-五四三三-我们赢了
that's right Akira! (clapping)
是的，晃！ （拍手）
We came to win!
我们来赢了！
- That is a very tired but determined man.
-这是一个非常疲倦但坚定的人。
- I love that Akira.
-我喜欢那晃。
- Seven grand's still on the table, take it whenever.
-桌上还有七个盛大的杯子，随时随地拿走。
Rope cutting time.
剪绳时间。
Once I start cutting some ropes,
一旦我开始割绳子，
one of you are gonna fall.
你们其中一个会倒下。
- Here we go! - One down.
- 开始了！ - 完成了一个。
- [Jake] That's two.
-[杰克]那是两个。
- [Host] Three down.
-[主持人]三倒。
Akira, make the call, you want one more?
晃，打个电话，你还要吗？
- [Akira] Yeah, do it.
-[Akira]是的。
- [Jake] Hey!
-[杰克]嘿！
- I don't know how many you're hanging on,
-我不知道你挂了多少
but it's not many.
但是数量不多。
All right, good luck!
好吧，祝你好运！
(upbeat synthesized music)
（欢乐的合成音乐）
Here you go, follow me.
在这里，跟随我。
- How far back we going?
-我们要走多远？
Are we going out here?
我们要出去吗？
- If he doesn't catch it, I cut another rope.
-如果他没抓住，我又剪了一根绳子。
- You gotta catch it, you ready?
-你要抓住它，准备好了吗？
- Yeah sure, why not?
-是的，为什么不呢？
- yeet
-还好
(ball bouncing)
（弹跳）
- So close.
- 很近。
- Marky Mark, Chandler disappeared, so, you're in charge.
-Marky Mark，Chandler不见了，所以，你来负责。
Here you go.
干得好。
- [Marcus] All right you ready Colby?
-[Marcus]好了，您准备好Colby吗？
- Right here, at me.
-就在我身边
- [Marcus] Oh!
-[马库斯]哦！
- Two ropes it is.
-是两根绳子。
- [Marcus] Oh my God, two ropes!
-[马库斯]天哪，两条绳子！
Red light me!
红灯亮我！
Here we go. (ominous instrumental music)
开始了。 （不祥的器乐）
One, two, three, four, five, six ropes.
一，二，三，四，五，六根绳子。
(ominous instrumental tones) (rope snapping)
（不祥的乐器音调）（跳绳）
Oh, now let's go to the other side.
哦，现在我们去另一边。
Knife me.
刀我
(ominous instrumental tones) (chuckling)
（不祥的乐器声）（咯咯笑）
Now there's four ropes,
现在有四根绳子，
should we just do one more on each side
我们应该在每一侧再做一次吗
and just get it done with?
并完成它？
Akira, do you agree?
晃，你同意吗？
- Yeah. - Okay.
-是的- 好的。
(grunting) (gasping)
（咕run）（喘气）
There are now three ropes remaining.
现在剩下三根绳子了。
(upbeat electronic music)
（欢乐的电子音乐）
- Win $7,000.
-赢得$ 7,000。
You know you gotta jump in the pool.
你知道你要跳进游泳池。
(upbeat electronic music)
（欢乐的电子音乐）
- You guys just don't budge.
-你们只是不让步。
What do you want me to do,
你想要我做什么，
just cut it down to one rope?
只是砍到一根绳子？
- Let's do it. - Let's do it?
- 我们开始做吧。 - 我们开始做吧？
- Yeah.
-是的
- Let's ask our consultant, Cameron.
-请问我们的顾问卡梅伦。
You were up there, you know how they feel,
你在那里，你知道他们的感觉，
should we go down to one rope?
我们应该下降到一根绳子吗？
- They've been up there quite some time so I say yeah.
-他们去那里已经有一段时间了，所以我说是的。
- Say no more, one rope.
-别再说了，一根绳子。
Red lights.
红灯。
Three ropes remain. (ominous instrumental music)
剩下三根绳子。 （不祥的器乐）
I know you feel a difference now.
我知道您现在感觉有所不同。
- Y'all feelin' that? - Yeah.
-你们都觉得吗？ -是的
- Okay, to the other side.
-好的，到另一边。
Still ten grand, anyone want it?
还是十个盛大，有人想要吗？
I'm trying to end your suffering so we cut one over there.
我正在尽力消除您的痛苦，所以我们在那边砍了一个。
(rope springing) (exclaiming)
（绳索弹跳）（惊呼）
One rope remains.
只剩一根绳子。
(upbeat electronic music)
（欢乐的电子音乐）
There's officially one rope left.
正式剩下一根绳子了。
We could cut the last rope and do last fall into water.
我们可以剪掉最后一根绳子，最后倒入水中。
- It'll be a shootout. - But I'd only do it
-枪战。 -但是我只会做
if you both agreed to it.
如果你们都同意的话。
You wanna do it Colby?
你想做科尔比吗？
- Well we might as well get it over with.
-好吧，我们还是可以克服它。
- So you're okay with me cutting the final rope?
-所以我可以剪最后一根绳子吗？
- Oh my God! - We're cutting
- 哦，我的上帝！ -我们在剪
the final rope!
最后的绳子！
- We're about to cut the rope,
-我们要剪绳子了，
what's going through your mind?
你在想什么
- I'm just thinking about my brothers, my family back home.
-我只是在想我的兄弟，我的家人回到家。
(sniffing) - Aw.
（嗅）-哇。
I'm cheering for you.
我为你加油。
So what's going through your mind Colby?
那么，科尔比在想什么呢？
How long do you think you'll hang?
你认为你会挂多久？
- Not very long, I'm a weak one so--
-没多久，我太弱了-
- Well you agreed to it, so we'll do it.
-好吧，您同意了，所以我们会做。
They both agreed to this, let it be known.
他们都同意这一点，让大家知道。
30-ish hours comes down to this.
30个小时的时间归结于此。
Jake and Marcus are gonna cut the rope on both sides
杰克和马库斯要剪断双方的绳索
at the same time and whoever can hang the longest wins.
在同一时间，谁可以挂最长的胜利。
Whoever loses will still get ten grand 'cause why not?
谁输了仍然会得到十个大奖，原因何在？
Three, two, one, cut!
三，二，一切！
(suspenseful orchestral music)
（管弦乐队的悬念音乐）
- Come on Colby! - Come on!
-加油！ - 来吧！
- You got this! - Pumped!
-你懂的！ -抽！
(instrumental music intensifying)
（乐器音乐愈演愈烈）
(shouting) (clapping)
（喊）（拍手）
- This could equal a million dollars.
-这可能等于一百万美元。
(shouting) (splashing)
（大喊）（溅起）
(exclaiming) (shouting)
（喊）（喊）
(water splashing) (cheering)
（泼水）（欢呼）
- I can't even move my legs.
-我什至不能动我的腿。
- But you just won $10,000 though.
-但是您赢了10,000美元。
- Yeah.
-是的
- And here is our winner!
-这是我们的赢家！
He's going on to compete for one million dollars
他将继续争取一百万美元
in a few weeks.
在几周之内。
If you want a chance to compete against him,
如果您想有机会与他竞争，
make sure you follow me on Instagram or buy merch.
确保您在Instagram上关注我或购买商品。
Three more of these,
其中三个，
all twelve people in the future three challenges,
未来十二个人全部面临三个挑战，
will be people that follow me on Instagram or buy merch.
将是在Instagram上关注我或购买商品的人。
You can face 'em, for one million dollars.
您可以花一百万美元面对他们。
- Now this was for my brother. (sniffing)
-现在这是给我哥哥的。 （嗅）
- I think we should call him.
-我想我们应该给他打电话。
- [Host] Yeah, let's see what he says.
-[主持人]是的，让我们看看他说的是什么。
- Guess what your brother did?
-我想我们应该给他打电话。 -猜猜你兄弟做什么？
- Oh my gosh, please tell me he won?
-天哪，请告诉我他赢了吗？
- [Host] Yeah he did, he got the dub.
-[主持人]是的，他做了，他得到了配音。
- Oh my goodness!
- 哦，我的天啊！
- I did it for you, bro 'cause I know,
-我为您做了，兄弟，因为我知道，
this means a lot to you
这对你意义重大
and I know you wish you could have been here.
我知道你希望你能来这里。
(sniffing) So I hung in there for you guys.
（嗅）所以我挂在你们那里。
I know it's gonna make our lives a lot better
我知道这会让我们的生活变得更好
if I can win that one mil.
如果我能赢得那一百万。
I'm gonna do it for us though.
我要为我们做。
(sniffing) Love you.
（嗅）爱你。
- Dang, I'm crying now, ooh my goodness.
-ang，我在哭，我的天哪。
So we'll see you again in a few weeks, later guys.
好，几周后，我们会再见。
Also don't forget we're still selecting for the next three
同样不要忘记，我们仍在选择接下来的三个
'Last to Leave' videos.
“最后离开”视频。
If you want to compete, follow me on Instagram
如果你想竞争，请在Instagram上关注我
or buy my merch.
或买我的商品。
Trust me guys, I care a lot about you international people
相信我，我非常关心你国际人
but when trying to comply with the laws in America
但是当试图遵守美国法律时
and other countries at the same time,
和其他国家同时
it's just hard, so sadly, this sweepstakes
这很难，可悲的是，这个抽奖活动
is only U.S. based.
仅基于美国。
Also quick add in, we have a big problem
还快速添加，我们有一个大问题
with people impersonating me and I will only DM you
人们冒充我，我只会向你DM
from my verified Mr. Beast Instagram account.
从我经过验证的Beast先生Instagram帐户中获取。
(exploding)
（爆炸）
♪ Mister Beast's six thousand ♪
♪野兽先生的六千♪
♪ Mister Beast's 6000 yeah ♪
♪野兽先生6000♪
♪ You know his name ♪
你知道他的名字
♪ He changed it once or twice ♪
♪他改变了一两次♪
♪ but I think it's here to stay ♪
♪但是我认为它会留下来♪
(exploding)
（爆炸）